<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2013 Brian D. Allred
  ~
  ~     This software source code is protected by copyright
  ~     and may not be used, modified, or distributed
  ~     without my permission.
  ~
  ~     All rights reserved.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Nexus BIOS Boot Installer</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_model">Select Model</string>
    <string name="title_os">Select Android Version</string>
    <string name="title_color">Select Animation Version</string>
    <string name="title_fps">FPS Slider</string>
    <string name="title_install">Preview/Install</string>
    <string name="title_preview">Animation Preview</string>
    <string name="title_install_1">Install</string>
    <string name="title_uninstall">Cleanup/Uninstall</string>
    <string name="about_header"><b>Nexus BIOS Boot Animation Installer</b></string>
    <string name="about_section">%1$s%1$sThanks for installing my boot animation installer! To get started, open the drawer to the left and tap Preview/Install.%1$s%1$sThis app is currently targeted at the Nexus 5, Nexus 7 2012, Nexus 7 2013, and Nexus 10. Animations for other Nexus devices are no longer planned due to age.%1$s%1$sThis app comes with no warranty or guarantee. I\'ve done the best I can to ensure no harm comes to your device, but that responsibility ultimately lies with you, the user.%1$s%1$sThis is for AOSP-based or CM-based ROMs ONLY! Consider yourself warned!%1$s%1$sCopyright © 2014 Brian Allred%1$sAll rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="about_fps">If the boot animation is too slow, increase this number. If it\'s too fast, decrease it.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="checkbox_force_play">Force at least one play-through of entire animation, even if device is done booting.</string>
    <string name="data_local_root">Recommended for unencrypted devices.\n\n/data/local is recommended because there\'s no existing animation here by default, so there\'s nothing to backup or save. AOSP/CM defaults to the animation in /data/local, then falls back to /system/media if it doesn\'t find one. It also persists through dirty ROM flashes. If you run the uninstallation for a /data/local animation, it simply deletes the animation.</string>
    <string name="data_local_non_root">This only works on *some* non-rooted devices. I can *not* guarantee it will work with yours.</string>
    <string name="system_media_root">Use only if /data/local didn\'t work for you or your device is encrypted.\n\n/system/media is not recommended because of a couple reasons. Namely, this is where the default boot animation lives, so making sure to backup the default animation in case updates check for modified /system partitions is important. Also, dirty ROM flashes will wipe /system, forcing you to reinstall the boot animation every time you dirty flash. The only time I would recommend /system/media is if the device is encrypted since the animation player can\'t read the encrypted /data/local partition during boot. Running uninstallation for a /system/media animation attempts to find the old animation and restore it. If it can\'t, it lets you know so you can either fix the issue manually or choose to revert to stock.</string>
    <string name="sysmte_media_non_root">Unavailable without root access.</string>

</resources>
